Guide to the Elmer J. Holland Papers, 1937-1968 AIS.1968.23
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Legislative Files, II.
  - Legislation Introduced, 1.
    - H. R. 9262- To Reclassify Certain Positions in the Postal Field Service, etc, April 26, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 9607- Moorhead Corbett, Holland re; Enlargement & Improvement of Bruceton Lab., May 3, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - H.R. 9824- For the Relief of Fayez S Tushan, Dr., May 9, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 9976- Amends Title VII of the Housing Act of 1961 to Authorize Federal Grants- Open Space, May 15, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - H.R. 10720- To Amend MDTA of 1962 to Provide Grants to State & Local Governments for the Development of Comprehensive Manpower Development & Utilization Plans, June 8, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 10942- Joint Sponsored: To Amend Title V of the Higher Ed Act of '66, June 16, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 11265- Perkins, Holland, etc- Authorize Appropriations for Adult Ed Act of 1966 for Two Additional Years, June 29, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 11280- Public Employment Service Act of 1967, June 29, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 11308- A Bill to Amend the National Foundation on the Arts & Humanities Act of '65, July 10, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - H. Res. 818- Concerning Rhodesia to Committee on Foreign Affairs, July 25, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 11945- To Amend the College Work-Study Program (Co-Sponsor), July 31, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 12120- For Prevention, Treatment, and Control of Juvenile Delinquency, August 7, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 12257- To Amend Vocational Rehabilitation Act, August 10, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 12280- "The Guaranteed Employment Act of 1967", August 10, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 12567- Technical Amendments to the Library Services and Construction Act, August 23, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 12882- To Provide Payment of Administrative Expenses for Safety Program under Longshoremen's & Harbor Worker's Comp, September 13, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 13048- Amendments to the Library Services and Construction Act, September 21, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 13054- "Age Discrimination in Employment Act of 1967", September 21, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 13123- To Amend the Elementary & Secondary Education Act of 1965, September 26, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 13369- To Amend Section 509 of the Merchant Marine Act of 1936, October 9, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 13562- To Require Reports to Congress of Certain Actions of the Federal Power Commission, October 18, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - H.J. Res. 895- Creating a Federal Committee on Nuclear Development, October 18, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 13689- To Amend the Longshoremen's & Harbor Compensation Act, October 25, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 13771- To Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1954 to Raise Needed Additional Revenues by Tax Reform, October 31, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - H. Res. 922- Re Witholding of House Salaries Until Such Time as Congress Appropriates Needed Funds for All Agencies, November 28, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 14314- Amends Section 302(c) of the Labor-Management Relations Act of 1947, December 6, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - H.R. 14521- To Amend Title 38 of the U.S. Code to Provide Increased Disability Comp., etc, December 15, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - H.R. 14558- To Provide for Compensation for Permanent Total Disability or Death from Exposure to Ionizing Radiation in Uranium Mines, December 15, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - H.R. 14816- The Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1968, January 28, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 15045- Amends the MDTA Act of 1962, February 1, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 15111- Food Supplement Amendment of 1967, February 6, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 15112- Federal Employee Labor-Management Act of 1968, February 6, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - H.J. Res. 1056- Making the Second Week in May "National School Safety Patrol Week", February 6, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 15198- Co-Sponsored with Mr. Perkins & Others- Amends Labor-Management Act, 1947, February 7, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 15398- To Amend the National School Lunch Act, February 19, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 15827- Vocational Rehabilitation Amendments of 1968, March 7, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 15891- Making a Supplemental Appropriation to Carry Out Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, March 12, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 16014- To Amend National Labor Relations Act as Amended, March 18, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 16302- "Uranium Miners' Compensation Act", March 28, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 16460- To Amend Vocational Education Act of 1963, April 3, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 16673- Re: A National Education Policy, April 22, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 16729- Extension of National Defense Student Loan Program, April 23, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 16770- Vocational Rehabilitation Amendments of 1968, April 24, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 16819- Vocational Rehabilitation Amendments of 1968 -- Supercedes 16770, April 25, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 17131- Youth Camp Safety Act, May 8, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 17145- "American Hunger Commission Act", May 8, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - H.J. Res. 1271- Re. White House Conference on Aging in 1971, May 14, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 18289- To Amend the Federal Aviation Act of 1968, July 2, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 18367- To Amend the Vocational Education Act of 1963, July 8, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 18410- To Amend the Randloph-Sheppard Vending Stand for the Blind Law so as to Make Certain Improvements Therein, July 9, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 18763- "Handicapped Children's Early Education Assistance Act", July 19, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 17748 - Occupational Safety & Health Act of 1968, June 10, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 17829- Handicapped Childrens' Early Education Assistance Act, June 12, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 17867- Older American Act of 1965 Amendments of 1968, June 13, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 17872- National School Lunch Act Amendments, June 13, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 17873- To Amend the National School Lunch Act, June 13, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 17916- Food Stamp Act of 1964 Amendments, June 17, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - H.J. Res. 1371- White House Conference on Aging in 1971, June 27, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Committees, 2.
    The Committees Subseries contains information regarding the committees on which he served.
    - Agriculture (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Armed Services (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - District (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Education and Labor General Information (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1967 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Rules of the Committee on Education and Labor; vote on major labor and educational bills (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Staff Report. "Report of an investigation...into the role of federally paid anti poverty workers in the Detroit Riot, June 23 28, 1967,", August 1967 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Staff Report. "Staff report of investigation involvement ofanti Poverty personnel in Newark, New Jersey, Racial Disturbances, 1967; Part of Investigation July 27-August 9 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Holland. Legislation H.R. 7819. (QUIE amendment to the Elementary and Secondary Education Act. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Information file: Labor (general) (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Information file: Labor Situs Picketing (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Information File: Library Services (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Information File: Minimum Wage (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Information File: National Labor Relations Act (Taft Hartley) Section 14(b) (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Information File: Overtime Work (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Information File: Poverty (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
    - Information File: Poverty (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Information File: Shorter Work Week (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Information File: 32 hour week (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Information File: Unemployment Compensation (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Information File: Vocational Training (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Information File: Washington, D.C. (Home Rule). (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Information File: Youth Employment Act and National Service Corps (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Education and Labor. Select Subcommittee on Labor Chairman. General. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Chairman. Correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Chairman. Memorandum. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Chairman. Statements, speeches. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Executive Session. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Statements before Committee. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Proposals. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Reports. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Committee correspondence, A (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Committee correspondence, B (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Committee correspondence, C (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Committee correspondence, D (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Committee correspondence, E (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Committee correspondence, F (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Committee correspondence, G (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Committee correspondence, H (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Committee correspondence, I (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Committee correspondence, J (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Committee correspondence, K (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Committee correspondence, L (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Committee correspondence, M (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Committee correspondence, Mc (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Committee correspondence, N (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Committee correspondence, O (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Committee correspondence, P (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Committee correspondence, Q (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Committee correspondence, R (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Committee correspondence, S (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Committee correspondence, T (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Committee correspondence, U (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Committee correspondence, V (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Committee correspondence, W (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Committee correspondence, X Y Z (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Employment Service (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Mine Safety (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Older American (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Education and Labor. Select Subcommittee on Labor. Manpower Training (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Committee Files on Manpower Training Legislation. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Legislation. H.R.7373 (1961) Manpower Development and Training Act. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Legislation. H.R.8399. Manpower Development and Training Act (Clean Bill pm H.R. 7373) (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Legislation H.R. 8399 Proposed Amendments (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Legislation H.R. 8399 Remarks before House Rules Committee, February 6, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Legislation H.R. 8399 Floor Fight, etc. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Legislation. H.R. 8399 Floor Speech and material (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Legislation. S1991 (Senate Version of H.R. 7373) (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Legislation. H.R. 8399 (Holland File) (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Legislation. H.R. 8720 (MDTA) Manpower Development and Training Act, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Legislation. H.R. 8720 (MDTA) Manpower Development and Training Act, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Legislation. H.R. 10363. MDTA, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Legislation. MDTA. General Information. (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
    - Legislation. H.R. 14690 (MDTA) Hearings, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - MDTA Reports and Speeches (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - President's Manpower Report Hearings. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Programs. General Projects. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Programs. Butler County (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Programs. McKeesport (Mon Yough) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Programs. Pittsburgh, 1963-1965 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
    - Pittsburgh (South Side), 1962-1964 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Programs. Pennsylvania. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Programs. Independent Garage Owners of Pennsylvania (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Reports. U.S. Department of Labor. Manpower Reports. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Commendation (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Complaint. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - MDTA Information File. MDTA Courses. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - MDTA Information File Retraining. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - MDTA Information File Retraining, Pittsburgh. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - MDTA Information File Retraining (complaints) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - MDTA Information File Pennsylvania (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Education and Labor Subcommittee on unemployment and the Impact of Automation (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Chairman (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Minutes (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Hearings (H.R. 7373) (Stenographic transcript) (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Hearings (Published) (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Report (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Summaries of report. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - New Release (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Legislation H.R.10310 National Commission of Technology, automation, and economic progress (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Legislation- S2274 National Economic Conversion Commission (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Automation Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Automation Correspondence Dr. Buckingham (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Automation Holland Automation and Impact of Automation (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Automation Holland Speeches (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Automation Holland Speech material (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Automation Report (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Automation Report material (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Automation Information File, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Automation Information File, 1962-1963 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Automation Information File Automation File, Awesome Servant. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Automation Information File Hospital (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Automation Information File Job eliminations and openings (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Automation Information File Retraining (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
    - Automation Information File Newspaper clippings, articles (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Automation Information File General (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Automation Information File General (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
    - Committee Files. Reference materials. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Committee Files. Reference materials. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Committee Files. Reference materials. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Committee Files. Reference materials. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Government Operations (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - House Administration (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Post Office and Civil Service (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Public Works (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Rules (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Science and Astronautics (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Un American Activities (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Veterans' Affairs (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Ways and Means (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Ways and Means (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Record (Remarks, Inserts, Etc), 3.
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Series II: Legislative File Subseries C. Congressional Records contained copies of the Congressional Record which were indexed by Congressman Holland's staff. These print copies were deaccessioned since the publication exists in microform. The user must consult the micro text edition held in the microforms area of the Hillman Library. A list prepared from the index headings compiled by the congressman's staff can be found in the collection's case file at the Archives Service Center.
    The Congressional Record Subseries contains Elmer J. Holland's remarks on the Congressional Record.
- Constituent Correspondence Files, III.
  Access Restrictions
  Series 3, Constituent Correspondence Files, Sub series A-H have been closed for research for 75 years after the date of the creation of the record. These files deal with armed services, immigration, positions, post office, service academies, veterans, and social security correspondence from Holland's constituents.
  Mrs. Holland, in giving the records to the Archives, requested that this portion of the file be closed for ten years; however, because of the confidential nature of the material the file will remain closed for 75 years after the date of the creation of the record.
  No access is permitted until that time unless the problem has been reviewed and a new determination made.
  The Constituent Correspondence Files contain letters to/from constituents relating to the armed services, immigration, post office, service academies, and veteran affairs.
  - Individuals, 1.
  - Armed Services, 2.
  - Immigration, 3.
  - Positions, 4.
  - Post Office, 5.
  - Service Academies, 6.
  - Veterans, 7.
  - Social Security, 8.
- Special Files, IV.
  The Special Files contains material relating to Elmer J. Holland's elections 1936-1967, local community records, and a subject file.
  - Elections, 1.
    The Elections Subseries contains material relating to Elmer J. Holland's elections 1936-1967.
    - 30th Congressional District. Wards Boroughs Townships. (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Reapportionment of Congressional Districts. (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Election Reform Act, 1966 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1936 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Campaign for City Council. (Holland), 1937 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Primary election returns for city council, 1937 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Certificate of election. Pennsylvania General Assembly, House of Representatives, 1938 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Campaign for City Council. (Holland), 1939 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1940 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Certificate of election. Pennsylvania General Assembly. House ofRepresentatives. Analysis of the votes cast at the general elections (City of Pittsburgh.), November 5, 1940 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Campaign material, 1942 (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Vote return, 38th State Sen. District. Certificate of election. PennsylvaniaGeneral Assembly. Senate. (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Excerpt from speech, Judge R.H. Smith, Ross for Governor rally. (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - Special Election statistics, 33rd Congressional District, 1946 (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - General Official returns general election. (Pittsburgh and Allegheny County), 1948 (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - General Campaign material mayoralty election, 1950 (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - Vote return, 38th State Senatorial District, 1950 (Box 196, Folder 19)
    - General Voter registration statistics as of municipal election by party affiliation, November 6, 1951 (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - General EJH correspondence and speeches, 1952 (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - General campaign material, 1952 (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Voter registration statistics, 1952 (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - School Straw vote, 1953 (Box 196, Folder 24)
    - Statistics, 1953 (Box 196, Folder 25)
    - General Election statistics, 1954 (Box 196, Folder 26)
    - Primary, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Special, January 24. EJH campaign and election to Congress, U.S. Representative, 30th Congressional District, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Special, January 24. Receipts and expenditures, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - EJH correspondence, releases, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Official election returns, 30th Congressional District, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Endorsements and campaign literature, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Receipts and expenditures, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Thank you letters, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - General EJH correspondence, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Endorsements, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Election statistics (Includes Allegheny County resume, Pres. Elections, senatorial and congressional election results), 1944-1956 (Box 198, File-cabinet 1)
    - Voter registration statistics (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Campaign literature (Box 198, Folder 3-5)
    - Contributions (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Expenditures (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - EJH Congratulations on elections (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Volunteers for Stevenson mailing list (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - EJH Badge. Democratic national convention, 1956 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings of election returns. Wilkinsburg Boro Election returns, 1957 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Primary Election statistics, 1958 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Endorsements (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Calendar, sample ballot, candidates (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Election statistics, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Election statistics, 30th Congressional District, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Voter registration, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Pre election statement of contributions and expenditures, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Endorsements, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Contributions and receipts, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Expenditures, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Emery Bacon vs. James Fulton, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Letters from corporations to employees and stockholders on candidates and investigation thereof, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Campaign material, 1958 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Questions, sample ballot, etc., 1958 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Primary Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - General County Commissioners. 30th Congressional District. Election Statistics., 1959 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Holland for Congress Committee, 1959 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Congressional general election statistics, 1954-1958 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Lists of elected officials (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Primary Correspondence, endorsements, election statistics, and general information, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Endorsements, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer workers, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Election statistics, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Voter registration, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Meetings, appointments, etc., 1960 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Holland for Congress Committee (Includes: contributions and expenditures), 1960 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Campaign material (Box 202, Folder 1-3)
    - Congratulations (Box 202, Folder 4-5)
    - City of McKeesport Election Statistics, 1956, 1958, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - General, 1961 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Holland for Congress Committee, 1961 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Election results (Newspaper clippings) and lists of elected officials, 1961 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Primary Voting, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Endorsements (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Holland for Congress Committee (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Campaign contributions (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Campaign material (Box 204, Folder 2-3)
    - Campaign expenditures (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Holland for Congress Committee, 1963 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - List of elected officials 30th Congressional District, 1963 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Primary Correspondence, 1964 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Endorsements and election returns (Newspaper) and misc., 1964 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Holland for Congress Committee, 1964 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Campaign contributions, 1964 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Expenditures, 1964 (Box 205, Folder 6)